{
  "name": ".exit-polls-data",
  "data": [
    {
      "year": 1972,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "Richard Nixon",
        "dem": "George McGovern"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.51,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "36",
                "rep": "61",
                "ind": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.49,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "38",
                "rep": "60",
                "ind": 2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.89,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "32",
                "rep": "66",
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.1,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "82",
                "rep": "18",
                "ind": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "64",
                "rep": "34",
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.46,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "61",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.19,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "35",
                "rep": "61",
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "7",
                "rep": "92",
                "ind": 1
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "28",
                "rep": "70",
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.28,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "65",
                "rep": "34",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "46",
                "rep": "51",
                "ind": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "59",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1972,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 1976,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "Gerald Ford",
        "dem": "Jimmy Carter"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.5,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -13,
                "demChange": 14,
                "change": 27
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.5,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -12,
                "demChange": 12,
                "change": 24
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.9,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -14,
                "demChange": 15,
                "change": 29
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.08,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "83",
                "rep": "16",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "76",
                "rep": "24",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": -10,
                "demChange": 12,
                "change": 22
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.41,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "77",
                "rep": "22",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -15,
                "demChange": 16,
                "change": 31
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.34,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "54",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 8,
                "change": 15
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.25,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "9",
                "rep": "90",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -15,
                "demChange": 16,
                "change": 31
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.3,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -11,
                "demChange": 10,
                "change": 21
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.03,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "64",
                "rep": "34",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "56",
                "rep": "41",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -10,
                "demChange": 10,
                "change": 20
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "43",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -11
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1976,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 1980,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "Ronald Reagan",
        "dem": "Jimmy Carter"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.5,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "36",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 9,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": -14,
                "change": -21
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.5,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "47",
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.88,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "35",
                "rep": "56",
                "ind": 9,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -12,
                "change": -16
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.09,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "85",
                "rep": "11",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "55",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": 13,
                "demChange": -21,
                "change": -34
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.63,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "36",
                "rep": "57",
                "ind": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.25,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "31",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 14
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.45,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "67",
                "rep": "26",
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -10,
                "change": -14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "30",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 15,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": -13,
                "change": -14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.3,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "9",
                "rep": "86",
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "35",
                "rep": "59",
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -9,
                "change": -13
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "50",
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": -12,
                "change": -18
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "39",
                "ind": 16,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": -19,
                "change": -24
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "52",
                "rep": "41",
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "41",
                "rep": "36",
                "ind": 23,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": -13,
                "change": -6
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1980,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 1984,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "Ronald Reagan",
        "dem": "Walter Mondale"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.49,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "37",
                "rep": "62",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.51,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "56",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": 9,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -10
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.88,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "35",
                "rep": "64",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 8,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.09,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "90",
                "rep": "9",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.01,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.62,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "34",
                "rep": "66",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": 9,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "37",
                "rep": "62",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": -1
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.38,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "74",
                "rep": "25",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "36",
                "rep": "63",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 8,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": -2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.36,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "7",
                "rep": "92",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": 0.59,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "33",
                "rep": "66",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.28,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "54",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": -1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "67",
                "rep": "31",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -8,
                "demChange": 22,
                "change": 30
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "57",
                "rep": "42",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "59",
                "rep": "40",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": 18,
                "change": 14
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": null,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "38",
                "rep": "62",
                "ind": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1984,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 1988,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "George H. W. Bush",
        "dem": "Michael Dukakis"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.48,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "41",
                "rep": "57",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": 9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.52,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "50",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 11
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.85,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "59",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.1,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "86",
                "rep": "12",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "69",
                "rep": "30",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "46",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 5
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "50",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": 0.08,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "56",
                "rep": "43",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": 0.3,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "57",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.19,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "37",
                "rep": "62",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.16,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "50",
                "ind": 2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.54,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "59",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": 13
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.31,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "39",
                "rep": "60",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.38,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "82",
                "rep": "17",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -8,
                "demChange": 8,
                "change": 16
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -8,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 15
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.36,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "8",
                "rep": "91",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": 0.57,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "59",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.28,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "64",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "65",
                "rep": "32",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -10,
                "demChange": 8,
                "change": 18
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "36",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": null,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "57",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": 9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1988,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 1992,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "George H. W. Bush",
        "dem": "Bill Clinton"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.47,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "41",
                "rep": "38",
                "ind": 21,
                "repChange": -19,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": 19
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.53,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 18,
                "repChange": -13,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": 9
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.87,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "39",
                "rep": "40",
                "ind": 21,
                "repChange": -19,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": 18
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.08,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "83",
                "rep": "10",
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "61",
                "rep": "25",
                "ind": 14,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": -8,
                "change": -3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": 0.01,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "31",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.01,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "57",
                "rep": "25",
                "ind": 18,
                "repChange": -24,
                "demChange": 11,
                "change": 35
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": 0.21,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "34",
                "ind": 23
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": 0.36,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "41",
                "rep": "38",
                "ind": 21
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": 0.3,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "39",
                "ind": 18
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": 0.13,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "39",
                "ind": 11
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": 0.25,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "36",
                "ind": 21,
                "repChange": -14,
                "demChange": -6,
                "change": 8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": 0.07,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "28",
                "ind": 18,
                "repChange": -15,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": 13
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": 0.29,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "41",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 22,
                "repChange": -20,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": 19
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.23,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "39",
                "rep": "41",
                "ind": 20,
                "repChange": -21,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 23
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.16,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "36",
                "ind": 14,
                "repChange": -14,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 16
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.53,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "39",
                "rep": "38",
                "ind": 23,
                "repChange": -21,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": 20
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "41",
                "ind": 19,
                "repChange": -19,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 20
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.38,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "77",
                "rep": "10",
                "ind": 13,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "38",
                "rep": "32",
                "ind": 30,
                "repChange": -23,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": 18
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "10",
                "rep": "73",
                "ind": 17,
                "repChange": -18,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 20
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": 0.56,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "37",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 19,
                "repChange": -15,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": 12
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 21,
                "repChange": -17,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": 14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "80",
                "rep": "11",
                "ind": 9,
                "repChange": -24,
                "demChange": 16,
                "change": 40
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.06,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "53",
                "rep": "26",
                "ind": 21,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": -12,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.07,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "18",
                "ind": 20,
                "repChange": -18,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": 18
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": 0.66,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "41",
                "ind": 19,
                "repChange": -16,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": 14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": 0.34,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "51",
                "rep": "30",
                "ind": 19
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": null,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "72",
                "rep": "14",
                "ind": 14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": 0.01,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": 0.18,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "8",
                "rep": "82",
                "ind": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": 0.47,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 20
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1992,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": 0.32,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "64",
                "rep": "12",
                "ind": 24
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 1996,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "Bob Dole",
        "dem": "Bill Clinton"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.48,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 13,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": -4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.52,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "38",
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": 9,
                "change": 8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.83,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "46",
                "ind": 11,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": -2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.1,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "84",
                "rep": "12",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "72",
                "rep": "21",
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 11,
                "change": 15
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": 0.01,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 9,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 12,
                "change": 19
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.01,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "64",
                "rep": "21",
                "ind": 15,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 11
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": 0.17,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "53",
                "rep": "34",
                "ind": 13,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": 10,
                "change": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": 0.33,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "41",
                "ind": 11,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": 0.34,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "42",
                "ind": 10,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": 0.16,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "43",
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": 0.24,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "51",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 14,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": 8,
                "change": 9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": 0.06,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "59",
                "rep": "28",
                "ind": 13,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "40",
                "ind": 12,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "46",
                "ind": 10,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.17,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "52",
                "rep": "40",
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": -2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.46,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "43",
                "ind": 13,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.37,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "47",
                "ind": 10,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": -3
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.39,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "84",
                "rep": "10",
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 22,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "13",
                "rep": "80",
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": 0.55,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "47",
                "ind": 11,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.29,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "53",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 10,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": 9,
                "change": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.03,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "78",
                "rep": "16",
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.06,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "60",
                "rep": "23",
                "ind": 17,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.07,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "59",
                "rep": "23",
                "ind": 18,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": 0.66,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "46",
                "ind": 10,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": -1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": 0.34,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "57",
                "rep": "31",
                "ind": 12,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": 5
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "66",
                "rep": "23",
                "ind": 11,
                "repChange": 9,
                "demChange": -6,
                "change": -15
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": 0.95,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "43",
                "ind": 10
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": 0.53,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "69",
                "rep": "24",
                "ind": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": 0.43,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "23",
                "rep": "61",
                "ind": 16
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "78",
                "rep": "17",
                "ind": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": 0.51,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "31",
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": -51,
                "demChange": 54,
                "change": 105
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": 0.36,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "34",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 14,
                "repChange": 15,
                "demChange": -9,
                "change": -24
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 1996,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": 0.07,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "23",
                "rep": "51",
                "ind": 26,
                "repChange": 39,
                "demChange": -41,
                "change": -80
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 2000,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "George W. Bush",
        "dem": "Al Gore"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.48,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "53",
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": 9,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -10
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.52,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "43",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -5
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.81,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "54",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 8,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.1,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "90",
                "rep": "9",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": 9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": 0.07,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 14,
                "demChange": -10,
                "change": -24
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "55",
                "rep": "41",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 12,
                "change": 19
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.01,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "55",
                "rep": "39",
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 18,
                "demChange": -9,
                "change": -27
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": 0.17,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "46",
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 12,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -17
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": 0.33,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 8,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": 0.36,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": 0.14,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "47",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": 0.21,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 14,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -17
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "59",
                "rep": "39",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 11,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": 0.32,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "51",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 11,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.24,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "51",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.18,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "52",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.46,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "57",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 14,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -18
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.39,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "86",
                "rep": "11",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "47",
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": 12,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": -10
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "8",
                "rep": "91",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 11,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -16
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": 0.55,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "56",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 9,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "47",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 10,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "79",
                "rep": "19",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.06,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "28",
                "ind": 10,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": -3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.09,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "60",
                "rep": "31",
                "ind": 9,
                "repChange": 8,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": "",
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": 0.65,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "53",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "57",
                "rep": "38",
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "70",
                "rep": "25",
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": 0.96,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "50",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": 0.65,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "61",
                "rep": "36",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 12,
                "demChange": -8,
                "change": -20
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": 0.31,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "20",
                "rep": "74",
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 13,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -16
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": 0.19,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "70",
                "rep": "26",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 9,
                "demChange": -8,
                "change": -17
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": 0.66,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 21,
                "demChange": -17,
                "change": -38
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": 0.12,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "33",
                "rep": "62",
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": 10,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2000,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "33",
                "rep": "58",
                "ind": 9,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": 10,
                "change": 3
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 2004,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "George W. Bush",
        "dem": "John Kerry"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.46,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.54,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "51",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.77,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "41",
                "rep": "58",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.11,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "88",
                "rep": "11",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": 0.08,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "53",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 9,
                "demChange": -9,
                "change": -18
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "56",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "40",
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": 0.17,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "45",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": 0.29,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "46",
                "rep": "53",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": 0.38,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": 0.16,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": 0.22,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 10,
                "demChange": -9,
                "change": -19
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": 0.32,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "46",
                "rep": "54",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -2
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "46",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.16,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "55",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 3
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.43,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "38",
                "rep": "61",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.34,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": -3
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": 0.23,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "60",
                "rep": "40",
                "ind": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": 0.22,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": 0.37,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "56",
                "ind": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": 0.15,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "57",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": 0.03,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "35",
                "rep": "63",
                "ind": 2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.37,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "89",
                "rep": "11",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.37,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "6",
                "rep": "93",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": 0.54,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "59",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.03,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "74",
                "rep": "25",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.07,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "74",
                "rep": "23",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 12,
                "change": 17
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.1,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "67",
                "rep": "31",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": 0.25,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "21",
                "rep": "78",
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": 0.53,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "51",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 0
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": 0.63,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "57",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": 0.37,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "58",
                "rep": "40",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": -1
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "77",
                "rep": "23",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": 0.96,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "46",
                "rep": "53",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": 0.49,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "10",
                "rep": "89",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 53,
                "demChange": -51,
                "change": -104
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": 0.46,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "86",
                "rep": "12",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -62,
                "demChange": 66,
                "change": 128
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "11",
                "rep": "89",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": 63,
                "demChange": -59,
                "change": -122
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": 0.43,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "13",
                "rep": "87",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": 35,
                "demChange": -32,
                "change": -67
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "72",
                "rep": "26",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -36,
                "demChange": 39,
                "change": 75
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2004,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": 0.17,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "92",
                "rep": "6",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -52,
                "demChange": 59,
                "change": 111
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 2008,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "John McCain",
        "dem": "Barack Obama"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.47,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 12
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.53,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "56",
                "rep": "43",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 10
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.74,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "43",
                "rep": "55",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.13,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "95",
                "rep": "4",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": 0.09,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "67",
                "rep": "31",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -13,
                "demChange": 14,
                "change": 27
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -9,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": 15
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.03,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "66",
                "rep": "31",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -9,
                "demChange": 12,
                "change": 21
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": 0.18,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "66",
                "rep": "32",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -13,
                "demChange": 12,
                "change": 25
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": 0.29,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "52",
                "rep": "46",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": 13
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": 0.37,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": 0.16,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "53",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -3
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": 0.2,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "52",
                "rep": "46",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "63",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -14,
                "demChange": 13,
                "change": 27
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": 0.31,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "51",
                "rep": "47",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 12
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.28,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": 8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.17,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "58",
                "rep": "40",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.39,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "58",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.35,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "51",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": 0.18,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "65",
                "rep": "32",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -8,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 13
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": 0.19,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "55",
                "rep": "43",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": 0.36,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 12
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": 0.2,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "48",
                "rep": "51",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": 12
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": 0.06,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "52",
                "rep": "46",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -17,
                "demChange": 17,
                "change": 34
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.39,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "89",
                "rep": "10",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.29,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "52",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.32,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "9",
                "rep": "90",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 6
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": 0.54,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "54",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "45",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 14
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "78",
                "rep": "21",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": 8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.06,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "73",
                "rep": "22",
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.12,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "75",
                "rep": "23",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -8,
                "demChange": 8,
                "change": 16
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "24",
                "rep": "74",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": 0.48,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "54",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": 0.66,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 5,
                "change": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": 0.34,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "65",
                "rep": "33",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 14
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": 0.04,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "70",
                "rep": "27",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -7,
                "change": -11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": 0.96,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "53",
                "rep": "45",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -8,
                "demChange": 7,
                "change": 15
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": 0.2,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "27",
                "rep": "71",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -18,
                "demChange": 17,
                "change": 35
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": 0.75,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "36",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 24,
                "demChange": -24,
                "change": -48
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": 0.01,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": 0.06,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "23",
                "rep": "75",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -12,
                "demChange": 10,
                "change": 22
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": 0.44,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "40",
                "rep": "59",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 33,
                "demChange": -32,
                "change": -65
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2008,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": 0.49,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "66",
                "rep": "31",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 25,
                "demChange": -26,
                "change": -51
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "year": 2012,
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "Mitt Romney",
        "dem": "Barack Obama"
      },
      "web_title": "",
      "results": [
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SEX",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "MEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_MALE",
              "total_value": 0.47,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "WOMEN",
              "web_title": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "total_value": 0.53,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "55",
                "rep": "44",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "RACE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "WHITE",
              "web_title": "RACE_WHITE",
              "total_value": 0.72,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "39",
                "rep": "59",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "BLACK",
              "web_title": "RACE_BLACK",
              "total_value": 0.13,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "93",
                "rep": "6",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -4
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "HISPANIC",
              "web_title": "RACE_HISP",
              "total_value": 0.1,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "71",
                "rep": "27",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -4,
                "demChange": 4,
                "change": 8
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "ASIAN",
              "web_title": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "total_value": 0.03,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "73",
                "rep": "26",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -9,
                "demChange": 11,
                "change": 20
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "RACE_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "58",
                "rep": "38",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 7,
                "demChange": -8,
                "change": -15
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CUBAN3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "AGE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "AGE_18-29",
              "total_value": 0.19,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "60",
                "rep": "37",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": -6,
                "change": -11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "AGE_30-44",
              "total_value": 0.27,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "52",
                "rep": "45",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "AGE_45-64",
              "total_value": 0.38,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "51",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65+",
              "web_title": "AGE_65+",
              "total_value": 0.16,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "56",
                "ind": 0,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "EDUC12R_HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "answer": "HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES",
              "web_title": "High school graduate",
              "total_value": 0.21,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "51",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": -3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "EDUC12R_NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "answer": "NO H.S. DIPLOMA",
              "web_title": "No high school diploma",
              "total_value": 0.03,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "64",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "total_value": 0.29,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "COLGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.29,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "47",
                "rep": "51",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "POSTGRAD",
              "web_title": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "total_value": 0.18,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "55",
                "rep": "42",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -5
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "WHITENONCOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "total_value": 0.36,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "36",
                "rep": "61",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "WHITECOLL",
              "web_title": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "total_value": 0.36,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "56",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 5,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -10
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "<$30,000",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "total_value": 0.2,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "63",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "30-49,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "total_value": 0.21,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "57",
                "rep": "42",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "50-99,999",
              "web_title": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "total_value": 0.31,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "46",
                "rep": "52",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "100-199,999",
              "web_title": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "total_value": 0.21,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "54",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_$200K+",
              "answer": "$200K+",
              "web_title": "$200,000 or more",
              "total_value": 0.07,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "44",
                "rep": "54",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 8,
                "demChange": -8,
                "change": -16
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PARTY",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "DEMOCRAT",
              "web_title": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "total_value": 0.38,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "92",
                "rep": "7",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "IND/OTHER",
              "web_title": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.29,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "45",
                "rep": "50",
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": -7,
                "change": -13
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "REPUBLICAN",
              "web_title": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "total_value": 0.32,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "6",
                "rep": "93",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -6
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "REL5",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "PROT/CHRIST",
              "web_title": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "total_value": 0.53,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "57",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "CATHOLIC",
              "web_title": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "total_value": 0.25,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "50",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "JEWISH",
              "web_title": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "69",
                "rep": "30",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 9,
                "demChange": -9,
                "change": -18
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "OTHER",
              "web_title": "REL5_OTHER",
              "total_value": 0.07,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "74",
                "rep": "23",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 0
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "NONE",
              "web_title": "REL5_NONE",
              "total_value": 0.12,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "70",
                "rep": "26",
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "WHITEBORNAGN",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "total_value": 0.26,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "21",
                "rep": "78",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "OTHERS",
              "web_title": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "total_value": 0.47,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "48",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -9
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_YES",
              "total_value": 0.6,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "42",
                "rep": "56",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -9
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "MARRIED_NO",
              "total_value": 0.4,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "62",
                "rep": "35",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -5
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LGBT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "YES",
              "web_title": "LGBT_YES",
              "total_value": 0.05,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "76",
                "rep": "22",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 6,
                "change": 11
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "NO",
              "web_title": "LGBT_NO",
              "total_value": 0.95,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "49",
                "rep": "49",
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRACK",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "RIGHTDIR",
              "web_title": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "total_value": 0.46,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "93",
                "rep": "6",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -65,
                "demChange": 66,
                "change": 131
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "WRONGTRACK",
              "web_title": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "total_value": 0.52,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "13",
                "rep": "84",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 48,
                "demChange": -49,
                "change": -97
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "NEC",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "EXCEL",
              "web_title": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "total_value": 0.02,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "",
                "rep": "",
                "ind": 100
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "GOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_GOOD",
              "total_value": 0.21,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "90",
                "rep": "9",
                "ind": 1,
                "repChange": -66,
                "demChange": 67,
                "change": 133
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "NOTGOOD",
              "web_title": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "total_value": 0.45,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "55",
                "rep": "42",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -17,
                "demChange": 15,
                "change": 32
              }
            },
            {
              "year": 2012,
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "POOR",
              "web_title": "NEC_POOR",
              "total_value": 0.31,
              "candidates": {
                "dem": "12",
                "rep": "85",
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 54,
                "demChange": -54,
                "change": -108
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "LIFE",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "QLT16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRCLIN",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "UNFAIRTRUMP",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TRUMPRESPECT",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "TIME16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "GOTV16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        },
        {
          "web_title": "",
          "question": "",
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": []
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "candidates": {
        "rep": "Donald J. Trump",
        "dem": "Hillary Clinton"
      },
      "sample_size": 24537,
      "results": [
        {
          "code": "SEX",
          "web_title": "Sex",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "y",
          "question": "Are you:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "24482",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "SEX_MALE",
              "answer": "Male",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.475926935031797",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 53,
                "dem": 41,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": -4,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "SEX_FEMALE",
              "answer": "Female",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.524073064968203",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 42,
                "dem": 54,
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": -1,
                "change": 1
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "RACE",
          "web_title": "Race",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "y",
          "question": "Are you:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "24193",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "RACE_WHITE",
              "answer": "White",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.703934747539192",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 58,
                "dem": 37,
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -1
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "RACE_BLACK",
              "answer": "Black",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.120891132307634",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 8,
                "dem": 88,
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -7
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "RACE_HISP",
              "answer": "Hispanic/Latino",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.112132472161782",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 29,
                "dem": 65,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -6,
                "change": -8
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "RACE_ASIAN",
              "answer": "Asian",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0367726967409582",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 29,
                "dem": 65,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -8,
                "change": -11
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "RACE_OTHER",
              "answer": "Other",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0262689512504343",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 37,
                "dem": 56,
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -1
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "AGE",
          "web_title": "Age",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "y",
          "question": "In which age group are you?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "24365",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "AGE_18-29",
              "answer": "18-29",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.191100101500173",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 37,
                "dem": 55,
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "AGE_30-44",
              "answer": "30-44",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.253293465963414",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 42,
                "dem": 50,
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "AGE_45-64",
              "answer": "45-64",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.400739953413552",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 53,
                "dem": 44,
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "AGE_65+",
              "answer": "65 or over",
              "web_title": "65 and over",
              "total_value": "0.154866479122861",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 53,
                "dem": 45,
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "EDUC12R",
          "web_title": "Education",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "y",
          "question": "Which best describes your education?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "23451",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "EDUC12R_HS",
              "answer": "High school or less",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.184940081649692",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 51,
                "dem": 45,
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "EDUC12R_SOMCOL/ASSOC",
              "answer": "Some college/assoc. degree",
              "web_title": "Some college/associate degree",
              "total_value": "0.318042202078012",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 52,
                "dem": 43,
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -6,
                "change": -10
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "EDUC12R_COLGRAD",
              "answer": "College graduate",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.315629196154217",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 45,
                "dem": 49,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 8
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "EDUC12R_POSTGRAD",
              "answer": "Postgraduate study",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.181388520118079",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 37,
                "dem": 58,
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": -5,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "EDUCWHITE",
          "web_title": "",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Education by race",
          "per_question_sample_size": "23172",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITECOLL",
              "answer": "White college graduates",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.366864853820589",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 49,
                "dem": 45,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": -7,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_WHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "White non-college graduates",
              "web_title": "White without a college degree",
              "total_value": "0.338341867590925",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 67,
                "dem": 28,
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": -8,
                "change": -14
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_NONWHITECOLL",
              "answer": "Non White college graduates",
              "web_title": "Nonwhite college graduates",
              "total_value": "0.130382298452102",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 23,
                "dem": 71,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "EDUCWHITE_NONWHITENONCOLL",
              "answer": "Non White non-college graduates",
              "web_title": "Nonwhite without a college degree",
              "total_value": "0.164410980136384",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 20,
                "dem": 75,
                "ind": 5
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "INCOME16GEN",
          "web_title": "Income",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "y",
          "question": "2015 total family income:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "9077",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_<$30,000",
              "answer": "Under $30,000",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.171718723763187",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 41,
                "dem": 53,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": -10,
                "change": -16
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_30-49,999",
              "answer": "$30,000 - $49,999",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.187466264088053",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 42,
                "dem": 51,
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": -6,
                "change": -6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_50-99,999",
              "answer": "$50,000 - $99,999",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.305953637379811",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 50,
                "dem": 46,
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": 0,
                "change": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_100-199,999",
              "answer": "$100,000 - $199,999",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.236884778923902",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 48,
                "dem": 47,
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 9
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_200-249,999",
              "answer": "$200,000 - $249,999",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.040262113366946",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 49,
                "dem": 48,
                "ind": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "INCOME16GEN_>$250,000",
              "answer": "$250,000 or more",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0577144824781015",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 48,
                "dem": 46,
                "ind": 6
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "SIZEPLC3",
          "web_title": "Residence",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "y",
          "question": "Population of area, three categories",
          "per_question_sample_size": "24537",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "SIZEPLC3_CITYOVER50K",
              "answer": "City over 50,000",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.336630800211853",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 35,
                "dem": 59,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "SIZEPLC3_SUBURBS",
              "answer": "Suburbs",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.492323719152278",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 50,
                "dem": 45,
                "ind": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "SIZEPLC3_SMCITY/RURAL",
              "answer": "Small city and Rural",
              "web_title": "Small city or rural",
              "total_value": "0.171045480635868",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 62,
                "dem": 34,
                "ind": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "PARTY",
          "web_title": "Party affiliation",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "No matter how you voted today, do you usually think of yourself as a:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "23400",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "PARTY_DEMOCRAT",
              "answer": "Democrat",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.365735227478989",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 9,
                "dem": 89,
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "PARTY_REPUBLICAN",
              "answer": "Republican",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.326493946055502",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 90,
                "dem": 7,
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "PARTY_IND/OTHER",
              "answer": "Independent or something else",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.307770826465509",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 48,
                "dem": 42,
                "ind": 10,
                "repChange": -2,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -1
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "PHIL3",
          "web_title": "Political ideology",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "On most political matters, do you consider yourself:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "22907",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "PHIL3_LIBERAL",
              "answer": "Liberal",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.262924789610012",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 10,
                "dem": 84,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "PHIL3_MODERATE",
              "answer": "Moderate",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.386161915767264",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 41,
                "dem": 52,
                "ind": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "PHIL3_CONSERV",
              "answer": "Conservative",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.350913294622725",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 81,
                "dem": 15,
                "ind": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "REL5",
          "web_title": "Religion",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Religion, combined Protestant and other Christian",
          "per_question_sample_size": "8246",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "REL5_PROT/CHRIST",
              "answer": "Protestant or other Christian",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.519219685758417",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 58,
                "dem": 39,
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 1,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "REL5_CATHOLIC",
              "answer": "Catholic",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.227180675294954",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 52,
                "dem": 45,
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 4,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -9
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "REL5_JEWISH",
              "answer": "Jewish",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0252638775395821",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 24,
                "dem": 71,
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 8
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "REL5_OTHER",
              "answer": "Something else",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0787759734044021",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 29,
                "dem": 62,
                "ind": 9,
                "repChange": 6,
                "demChange": -12,
                "change": -18
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "REL5_NONE",
              "answer": "None",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.149559788002645",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 26,
                "dem": 68,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 0,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "WHTEVANG",
          "web_title": "",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "White evangelical or white born-again Christians",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4802",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "WHTEVANG_WHITEBORNAGN",
              "answer": "White evangelical or white born-again Christian",
              "web_title": "Yes",
              "total_value": "0.260319040242849",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 81,
                "dem": 16,
                "ind": 3,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -5,
                "change": -8
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "WHTEVANG_OTHERS",
              "answer": "All others",
              "web_title": "No",
              "total_value": "0.739680959757151",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 35,
                "dem": 59,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": -13,
                "demChange": 10,
                "change": 23
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "ATTEND16",
          "web_title": "Attend religious services",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "How often do you attend religious services?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4559",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "ATTEND16_ONCEAWEEKORMORE",
              "answer": "Once a week or more",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.330344280030791",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 56,
                "dem": 40,
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "ATTEND16_AFEWAMONTH",
              "answer": "A few times a month",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.161575526242541",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 49,
                "dem": 46,
                "ind": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "ATTEND16_AFEWAYEAR",
              "answer": "A few times a year",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.288246142038808",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 47,
                "dem": 48,
                "ind": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "ATTEND16_NEVER",
              "answer": "Never",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.21983405168786",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 31,
                "dem": 62,
                "ind": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "MARRIED",
          "web_title": "Married",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "y",
          "question": "Are you currently married?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "9455",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "MARRIED_YES",
              "answer": "Yes",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.584862951897692",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 53,
                "dem": 43,
                "ind": 4,
                "repChange": -3,
                "demChange": 1,
                "change": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "MARRIED_NO",
              "answer": "No",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.415137048102308",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 38,
                "dem": 55,
                "ind": 7,
                "repChange": 3,
                "demChange": -7,
                "change": -10
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "LGBT",
          "web_title": "Gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Are you gay, lesbian, bisexual or transgender?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4527",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "LGBT_YES",
              "answer": "Yes",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0454513727876324",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 14,
                "dem": 78,
                "ind": 8,
                "repChange": -8,
                "demChange": 2,
                "change": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "LGBT_NO",
              "answer": "No",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.954548627212368",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 48,
                "dem": 47,
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": -1,
                "demChange": -2,
                "change": -1
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "VETVOTER",
          "web_title": "U.S. military service",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Have you ever served in the U.S. military?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4561",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "VETVOTER_YES",
              "answer": "Yes",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.134382628728617",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 61,
                "dem": 34,
                "ind": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "VETVOTER_NO",
              "answer": "No",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.865617371271383",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 45,
                "dem": 50,
                "ind": 5
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "TRACK",
          "web_title": "Direction of country",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Do you think things in this country today are:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4658",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "TRACK_RIGHTDIR",
              "answer": "Generally going in the right direction",
              "web_title": "Generally right direction",
              "total_value": "0.332718769942961",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 8,
                "dem": 90,
                "ind": 2,
                "repChange": 2,
                "demChange": -3,
                "change": -5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TRACK_WRONGTRACK",
              "answer": "Seriously off on the wrong track",
              "web_title": "Seriously off track",
              "total_value": "0.623055533254902",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 69,
                "dem": 25,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": -15,
                "demChange": 12,
                "change": 27
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "ISSUE16",
          "web_title": "Most important issue",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "y",
          "question": "Which ONE of these four issues is the most important facing the country? (CHECK ONLY ONE)",
          "per_question_sample_size": "9672",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "ISSUE16_FOREIGNPOLICY",
              "answer": "Foreign policy",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.128356510877801",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 34,
                "dem": 60,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "ISSUE16_IMMIGRATION",
              "answer": "Immigration",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.126035733800937",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 64,
                "dem": 32,
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "ISSUE16_ECONOMY",
              "answer": "The economy",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.521585561833334",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 42,
                "dem": 52,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "ISSUE16_TERRORISM",
              "answer": "Terrorism",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.181106627536326",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 57,
                "dem": 39,
                "ind": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "NEC",
          "web_title": "Condition of the nation's economy",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Do you think the condition of the nation's economy is:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4859",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "NEC_EXCEL",
              "answer": "Excellent",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0327611255534291",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 16,
                "dem": 83,
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "NEC_GOOD",
              "answer": "Good",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.331121682691752",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 19,
                "dem": 76,
                "ind": 5,
                "repChange": 10,
                "demChange": -14,
                "change": -24
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "NEC_NOTGOOD",
              "answer": "Not so good",
              "web_title": "Fair",
              "total_value": "0.412434547812523",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 55,
                "dem": 39,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": 13,
                "demChange": -16,
                "change": -29
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "NEC_POOR",
              "answer": "Poor",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.213400130953905",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 79,
                "dem": 15,
                "ind": 6,
                "repChange": -6,
                "demChange": 3,
                "change": 9
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "FINSIT",
          "web_title": "Family financial situation",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Compared to four years ago, is your family's financial situation:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4695",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "FINSIT_BETTER",
              "answer": "Better today",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.308783661132293",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 24,
                "dem": 72,
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "FINSIT_WORSE",
              "answer": "Worse today",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.269929849772194",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 78,
                "dem": 19,
                "ind": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "FINSIT_SAME",
              "answer": "About the same",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.406462889698574",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 46,
                "dem": 46,
                "ind": 8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "LIFE",
          "web_title": "What do you expect for the next generation of Americans?",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Do you expect life for the next generation of Americans to be:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4898",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "LIFE_BETTER",
              "answer": "Better than life today",
              "web_title": "Better than life today",
              "total_value": "0.36914763508326",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 38,
                "dem": 59,
                "ind": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "LIFE_WORSE",
              "answer": "Worse than life today",
              "web_title": "Worse than life today",
              "total_value": "0.336213150538737",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 63,
                "dem": 31,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "LIFE_SAME",
              "answer": "About the same",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.242074098093277",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 39,
                "dem": 54,
                "ind": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "TRADE16",
          "web_title": "Effect of trade with other countries on U.S. jobs",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Overall, would you say trade with other countries:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4898",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "TRADE16_CREATESJOBS",
              "answer": "Creates more U.S. jobs",
              "web_title": "Creates more jobs",
              "total_value": "0.382706793123948",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 35,
                "dem": 59,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TRADE16_TAKESJOBS",
              "answer": "Takes away U.S. jobs",
              "web_title": "Takes away jobs",
              "total_value": "0.417662969811237",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 65,
                "dem": 31,
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TRADE16_NOEFFECT",
              "answer": "Has no effect on U.S. jobs",
              "web_title": "Has no effect",
              "total_value": "0.111169867000362",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 30,
                "dem": 63,
                "ind": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "IMMDEPORT",
          "web_title": "What should happen to most illegal immigrants working in the U.S.?",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Should most illegal immigrants working in the United States be:",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4754",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "IMMDEPORT_LEGAL",
              "answer": "Offered a chance to apply for legal status",
              "web_title": "Offer chance to become legal",
              "total_value": "0.698725300255273",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 34,
                "dem": 60,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "IMMDEPORT_DEPORT",
              "answer": "Deported to the country they came from",
              "web_title": "Deport",
              "total_value": "0.253092908282052",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 84,
                "dem": 14,
                "ind": 2
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "IMMWALL",
          "web_title": "Building a wall along the entire U.S. border with Mexico",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "How do you feel about building a wall along the entire U.S. border with Mexico?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4695",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "IMMWALL_SUPPORT",
              "answer": "Support",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.408311514152732",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 86,
                "dem": 10,
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "IMMWALL_OPPOSE",
              "answer": "Oppose",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.539237408062359",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 17,
                "dem": 76,
                "ind": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "GOVTANGR16",
          "web_title": "Feelings about how the federal government is working",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Which best describes your feelings about the way the federal government is working?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "5002",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "GOVTANGR16_ENTHUSIASTIC",
              "answer": "Enthusiastic",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.054643224924738",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 20,
                "dem": 78,
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "GOVTANGR16_SATISFIED",
              "answer": "Satisfied, but not enthusiastic",
              "web_title": "Satisfied",
              "total_value": "0.237579234731339",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 20,
                "dem": 75,
                "ind": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "GOVTANGR16_DISSATISFIED",
              "answer": "Dissatisfied, but not angry",
              "web_title": "Dissatisfied",
              "total_value": "0.463089883255097",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 49,
                "dem": 45,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "GOVTANGR16_ANGRY",
              "answer": "Angry",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.229469718872302",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 77,
                "dem": 18,
                "ind": 5
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "OBAMA2",
          "web_title": "Obama's job performance",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Do you approve or disapprove of the way Barack Obama is handling his job as president?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4813",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "OBAMA2_APPROVE",
              "answer": "Approve",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.531977913817851",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 10,
                "dem": 84,
                "ind": 6
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "OBAMA2_DISAPPROVE",
              "answer": "Disapprove",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.452814861703301",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 90,
                "dem": 6,
                "ind": 4
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "DESCRIBP12",
          "web_title": "Best description of vote",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Which best describes your vote for president today?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4859",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "DESCRIBP12_FAVOR",
              "answer": "I strongly favor my candidate",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.412158872211493",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 42,
                "dem": 53,
                "ind": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "DESCRIBP12_RESERV",
              "answer": "I like my candidate but with reservations",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.318015948882874",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 49,
                "dem": 48,
                "ind": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "DESCRIBP12_DISLIKE",
              "answer": "I dislike the other candidates",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.250570409227417",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 51,
                "dem": 39,
                "ind": 10
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "QLT16",
          "web_title": "Most important candidate quality",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Which ONE of these four candidate qualities mattered most in deciding how you voted for president? (CHECK ONLY ONE)",
          "per_question_sample_size": "9672",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "QLT16_CARES",
              "answer": "Cares about people like me",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.153245804648725",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 35,
                "dem": 58,
                "ind": 7
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "QLT16_CHANGE",
              "answer": "Can bring needed change",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.393122743818638",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 83,
                "dem": 14,
                "ind": 3
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "QLT16_EXPERIENCE",
              "answer": "Has the right experience",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.214485138704987",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 8,
                "dem": 90,
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "QLT16_JUDGMENT",
              "answer": "Has good judgment",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.201146772759744",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 26,
                "dem": 66,
                "ind": 8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "CHIEF16",
          "web_title": "Better commander in chief",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Regardless of how you voted today, who would be a better commander in chief?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4695",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "CHIEF16_CLINTON",
              "answer": "Hillary Clinton",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.486272813958253",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 2,
                "dem": 94,
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "CHIEF16_TRUMP",
              "answer": "Donald Trump",
              "web_title": "Donald J. Trump",
              "total_value": "0.464609519593128",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 96,
                "dem": 1,
                "ind": 3
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "TEMPCLINTON",
          "web_title": "",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Do you think Hillary Clinton has the temperament to serve effectively as president?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4859",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "TEMPCLINTON_YES",
              "answer": "Yes",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.548342808429716",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 13,
                "dem": 82,
                "ind": 5
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TEMPCLINTON_NO",
              "answer": "No",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.434884499212954",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 89,
                "dem": 5,
                "ind": 6
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "TEMPTRUMP",
          "web_title": "Do you think Donald J. Trump has the temperament to serve effectively as president?",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Do you think Donald Trump has the temperament to serve effectively as president?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4859",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "TEMPTRUMP_YES",
              "answer": "Yes",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.349728184922526",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 94,
                "dem": 5,
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TEMPTRUMP_NO",
              "answer": "No",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.628786487801976",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 20,
                "dem": 72,
                "ind": 8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "CLINHONEST",
          "web_title": "",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Do you think Hillary Clinton is honest and trustworthy?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4859",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "CLINHONEST_YES",
              "answer": "Yes",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.361811128260888",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 4,
                "dem": 94,
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "CLINHONEST_NO",
              "answer": "No",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.610856387406718",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 73,
                "dem": 20,
                "ind": 7
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "TRUMPHONEST",
          "web_title": "Is Donald J. Trump honest and trustworthy?",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "Do you think Donald Trump is honest and trustworthy?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4859",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "TRUMPHONEST_YES",
              "answer": "Yes",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.332734922019445",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 94,
                "dem": 5,
                "ind": 1
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TRUMPHONEST_NO",
              "answer": "No",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.634281474873126",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 21,
                "dem": 71,
                "ind": 8
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "TIME16",
          "web_title": "Decided how to vote",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "When did you finally decide for whom to vote in the presidential election?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "4813",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "TIME16_LASTFEWDAYS",
              "answer": "In the last few days",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0769588449740542",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 46,
                "dem": 44,
                "ind": 10
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TIME16_LASTWEEK",
              "answer": "In the last week",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0557488213673726",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 50,
                "dem": 38,
                "ind": 12
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TIME16_OCTOBER",
              "answer": "In October",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.124742333096059",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 51,
                "dem": 37,
                "ind": 12
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TIME16_SEPTEMBER",
              "answer": "In September",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.125271729049679",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 50,
                "dem": 46,
                "ind": 4
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "TIME16_BEFORE",
              "answer": "Before that",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.602769570365034",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 45,
                "dem": 52,
                "ind": 3
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "code": "2WAYPRES16",
          "web_title": "Vote in a two-candidate race",
          "use": "y",
          "print_use": "",
          "question": "If these were the only two candidates for president on the ballot today, for whom would you have voted?",
          "per_question_sample_size": "9298",
          "exit_poll_subcategories": [
            {
              "code": "2WAYPRES16_CLINTON",
              "answer": "Hillary Clinton (Dem)",
              "web_title": "Hillary Clinton",
              "total_value": "0.472411564381271",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 1,
                "dem": 97,
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "2WAYPRES16_TRUMP",
              "answer": "Donald Trump (Rep)",
              "web_title": "Donald J. Trump",
              "total_value": "0.470195156296644",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 97,
                "dem": 1,
                "ind": 2
              }
            },
            {
              "code": "2WAYPRES16_WOULDNOTVOTE",
              "answer": "Would not have voted",
              "web_title": "",
              "total_value": "0.0460966662840574",
              "candidates": {
                "rep": 21,
                "dem": 16,
                "ind": 63
              }
            }
          ]
        }
      ],
      "year": 2016
    }
  ]
}